(Howard:)Bernie's having a girls' night
on Friday at our place.
(Howard:)You want to do something?
(Raj:)-Actually, I'm busy.
-Doing what?
(Raj:)There's a new sports bar
over on Colorado Ave.
(Howard:)-You're going to girls' night.
-Yeah.
(Howard:)You know
they're making jewelry, right?
(Raj:)You think they came up with that?
(Raj:)They were going
to drink beer and play darts.
(Leonard:)-What's up?
-Not his testosterone levels.
(Raj:)Excuse me. I happen to be very
comfortable with my masculinity.
(Howard:)How is that possible?
(Leonard:)Hey, I got an email
from Professor Proton.
Goody! What's it say?
(Leonard:)He's working on a paper
about nano vacuum tubes,
(Leonard:)and wants to know
if I'd take a look at it.
(Sheldon:)That's strange,
(Sheldon:)that he would come to you
for that and not me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I got two emails from him.